cowboom.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy

CowBoom is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to this web site. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this CowBoom-operated website. 

**CowBoom Privacy Statement**  
This privacy statement describes the measures we have taken to safeguard and protect your privacy, while providing you with a unique and rewarding online experience. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. This website uses cookies to keep track of items in your shopping cart during your website visit. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Our websites and mobile applications are not designed to respond to "do not track" requests from browsers. Information collected by CowBoom is used for the purposes of processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes and for improving this CowBoom-operated website and its performance. This CowBoom-operated website uses secure order forms for customers to request information, to trade items, or purchase products. We may request personally identifiable information such as customer's contact information (like your name, email address, address, telephone number) and financial information (like your credit card information). Contact information collected from secure online forms is used to send orders and information about our company to our clients and fulfillment partners. Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for products and services. 

**Security**  
This site has taken certain security measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. CowBoom has implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information. Your personally identifiable information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights. When you place orders or access your personally identifiable information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information supplied by you is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and securely stored in CowBoom's database. 

**Service Providers and CowBoom's Information Sharing Practices**  
CowBoom uses third party service providers to receive and inspect your shipped product, fill and deliver your order, charge your credit card, provide customer service, and to enhance your shopping experience by displaying ads based on your interests. To help us understand and enhance our interactions with you, we may permit providers (such as web analytic providers, advertising companies and others) to collect personal and other information about your online activities over time on our websites and online services and across other sites on the internet. 

Third party service providers and suppliers are required to keep confidential any personally identifiable information received on behalf of CowBoom and are not to use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us. 

Where applicable, CowBoom may disclose personally identifiable information to its product suppliers for the purposes of automated manufacturer warranty registration, sales reporting, and third party warranty registration.

We may also share personally identifiable information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, and other legal action, or if CowBoom reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect CowBoom, its customers or the public. 

**CowBoom does not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to others.**

**Interest-Based Advertising**  
Our service providers may use cookies to deliver customized ads based on your visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of these cookies. All such service providers are listed below. For additional information on these service providers and the opt-out process, follow the link indicated.

**Co-branded Sites**  
Co-branded sites are websites that CowBoom hosts, operates and manages for its clients under the client's logo or trademarks. We collect customer data and share certain personally identifiable information as appropriate with our respective clients based on their disclosed privacy policies.

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
Please note that CowBoom has links to other web sites. When you click on one of these links, you leave CowBoom and go to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these sites, to which we link, as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
This CowBoom-operated website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

For removal from all future email notifications from CowBoom, send an email to [ CustomerService@cowboom.com](mailto:CustomerService@cowboom.com) with the words "unsubscribe" in the subject line. 

**Correct/Update**  
To change, update or correct customer profile information, or notification preferences previously provided, you will need to login to http://www.cowboom.com and change the information previously provided to us. 

**Notification of changes**  
From time to time, we may choose to change our privacy practices and this Privacy Statement. We will notify you of material changes to the Privacy Statement by posting a revised Privacy Statement at this Web Site. We recommend that you check back at this Web Site on a periodic basis to review the then current Privacy Statement.

**Contacting the Web site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can email [support@cowboom.com](mailto:support@cowboom.com). Your email address and comments will only be used to respond to your inquiry and will not be saved. 

Last modified: January 1st, 2014
